

SHADRACK NGETICH

Software Developer

Experience: 4 years | **Available:** 1 Week | **Location:** Nairobi

ngetichk7@gmail.com | +254729314341

ABOUT ME



Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the publishing industry. Skilled in Javascript, react js, C#, php frameworks, Java, PostgreSQL, HTML5, Oracle Database, Databases, Curriculum Development, Web Design, and Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC). Strong engineering professional graduated from Meru university of science and technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Longhorn Publishers PLC

Mid level | Software Developer Nairobi , Kenya 2019-03-01 | 2019-12-01

Developing Digital eLearning platform as well as maintaining the existing database

Zenith Business Solution

Graduate trainee | Software Developer Nairobi , Kenya 2016-04-01 | 2019-02-01

I was task to develop healthcare system, deploy, write both technical and user documentation and maintain the systems.

EDUCATION



Meru University of Science and Technology

Bachelor | Bachelor of science in Computer Science

Awards: Second Class Upper Division

Meru University of Science and Technology

Masters | Masters

Pursuing masters degree in computer science



314

Database Android C#

Java JavaScript Linux servers

Windows Servers Kotlin PHP

LANGUAGE SKILLS

34/

English

Swahili